<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2012, 2016 PDT Extension Group and others.

    This program and the accompanying materials are made
    available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License 2.0
    which is available at https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-2.0/

    SPDX-License-Identifier: EPL-2.0
   
    Contributors:
        PDT Extension Group - initial API and implementation
 -->

<contexts>
   <context id="help_project_wizard_autoload" title="Specifying your psr-0 autoload settings">
        <description>This page lets you configure the psr-0 namespace for your project. It will automatically map to the &quot;src&quot; folder in the root of your project.

By providing psr-0 compatible autoloading in your project, the composer plugin will be able to determine the namespaces for your classes automatically.</description>
        <topic label="Composer Autoloading support" href="http://getcomposer.org/doc/04-schema.md#autoload"/>
        <topic label="PHP-FIG PSR-0 Standard" href="https://github.com/php-fig/fig-standards/blob/master/accepted/PSR-0.md"/>
   </context>
   <context id="help_project_wizard_basic" title="Basic composer configuration">
      <description>The values contained in this page will be used to initialize a new composer.json file in the root of your project.

By default, the value from the &quot;Vendor name&quot; will be set as the psr-0 namespace, with the first letter capitalized - this can be customized on the second page of the wizard.

The PHP version selected on this page will be set as a requirement in your composer.json file.

During project creation, a composer.phar will be automatically downloaded from getcomposer.org, and &quot;composer.phar dumpautoload&quot; will be executed to initialize the autoloading of your project.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="help_context_wizard_template_firstpage">
      <description>This Wizard allows you to initialize a new composer project from an existing package using the &quot;create-project&quot; command.

If you want to override the composer.json values from the target package, check the corresponding option on the left.</description>
      <topic href="http://getcomposer.org/doc/03-cli.md#create-project" label="Learn more about the create-project command"/>
   </context>
   <context id="help_context_wizard_template_secondpage" title="Selecting an existing Composer package">
      <description>Type in the search field on the left to search for packages on packagist.org. Click the &quot;Download&quot; button to select a specific package for installation and choose the desired version from the dropdown to the right.

Use the &quot;Select projects only&quot; check box to show only packages with the package type &quot;project&quot;.

By clicking on the &quot;Favorite&quot; button the selected package will open in a new browser window on packagist.org.</description>
      <topic href="http://getcomposer.org/doc/04-schema.md#type" label="Learn more about package types"/>
      <topic href="https://packagist.org/about" label="Learn how to register your package on packagist.org"/>
   </context>
   <context id="help_context_wizard_importer" title="Composer Import Wizard">
      <description>This wizard helps you to setup an existing Composer project in Eclipse. Just select the folder containing your project, and the importer will 

- Create a new eclipse project in your workspace
- Setup your project with the corresponding builders and facets
- Configure your buildpath automatically</description>
   </context>
</contexts>
